<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Deepu's Portfolio]]></title><description><![CDATA[Deepu's portfolio built with Astro using React and Tailwind CSS]]></description><link>https://example.com/</link><language>en-us</language><item><title><![CDATA[Real-Time Chat Experience]]></title><link>https://example.com/posts/chat-app/</link><guid>https://example.com/posts/chat-app/</guid><description><![CDATA[Created a straightforward Real-Time Chat Application using Node.js and Socket.IO. Upon visiting the website, users are prompted to enter their name and can instantly engage in chat. It's a minimalistic setup where users can freely communicate in real-time. However, please note that as there's no chat history storage, once the user leaves the website, the chat history is not retained. A basic and immediate platform for group conversations!]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ratings-Driven Hotel Recommendations]]></title><link>https://example.com/posts/hotel-recommendation/</link><guid>https://example.com/posts/hotel-recommendation/</guid><description><![CDATA[Engineered a Ratings-Driven Hotel Recommendation System using Python. Trained a model to predict and stored hotel recommendations based on user preferences and location, emphasizing higher ratings.The accompanying Flask app enables users to input a location, presenting a curated list of hotels with higher ratings for a personalized and enjoyable stay.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[User-Friendly Transport Management Tool]]></title><link>https://example.com/posts/transport-app/</link><guid>https://example.com/posts/transport-app/</guid><description><![CDATA[Developed an accessible Transport Management System using Flask, Python, and SQLite. This user-friendly tool allows anyone to seamlessly input vehicle details, including vehicle number, load, and date. The system efficiently stores this information in SQLite, providing users with insightful reports on their vehicle movements and destinations on specific dates. Streamlining logistics made easy!]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>